Ibijolaade Kofoworola Fayinminnu

Lagos State, 100215

Phone: 09054626842

Email: fayinminnuibijolaade@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Highly motivated and dedicated Customer Service Representative with 1 year of experience in providing exceptional customer service. Seeking to utilize my strong communication skills, problemsolving abilities, and passion for helping customers to contribute to the success of The Customer Focused Company

Skills:

- Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- Google Drive
- Report Writing
- Teamwork
- Willingness to learn
- Customer Service
- Strong organizational skills
- Git hub
- HTML
- CSS

Work Experience:

Training and Admin Assistant

The Customer Focused Company Ltd., Maryland, Lagos State

July 2022 – July 2023

- Utilized Microsoft Office applications, including Word, Excel, and PowerPoint, to support training and administrative tasks.
- Maintained training records, including trainee lists, schedules, and attendance sheets.
- Provided frontline support to customers, answering inquiries and resolving issues in a friendly and efficient manner.
- Handled escalated customer complaints with tact and professionalism, investigating and resolving issues to the satisfaction of the customer.

- Assisted in organizing and setting up classrooms for training sessions.
- Compiled training reports to track customer service culture initiatives.
- Responded to customer inquiries via phone and email, providing accurate and helpful information to resolve issues and address concerns promptly.

Teaching Assistance

Chari Maigumeri Barracks, Army Day Secondary School (NYSC), Lokoja, Kogi State

October 2021 - April 2022

- Provided support in teaching Biology to SS1 and SS2 students.
- Assisted in the dissection of rabbit practicals for SS2 and SS3 classes.
- Supported teachers in maintaining a positive learning environment and managing classroom activities.
- Assessed student assignments and provided feedback.

Computer Operator/Office Assistant

Ministry of Education, Science and Technology (NYSC), Lokoja, Kogi State

September 2018 - January 2019

- Set up computers and assisted with Microsoft Excel data collation for schools in Kogi State.
- Helped in registering students for NECO, BECE, and Common Entrance examinations.
- Took meeting minutes and provided general office support.

Internship

University College Hospital (UCH), Ibadan, Oyo

September 2018 - January 2019

- Assisted with safe transfusions of blood by conducting tests and completing blood counts.
- Set up, maintained, and ensured the sterility of laboratory equipment and tools.
- Analyzed experiment and test results to validate adherence to standards and specifications.
- Prepared samples for shipping and disposed of bodily fluids in compliance with safety guidelines.
- Participated in community health voluntary services during medical outreach programs.

Education:

Bachelor of Science: Biochemistry

Wesley University, Ondo City

September 2015 - August 2019

- Second Class Upper (2.1)
- Relevant coursework: Biochemical Toxicology, Advanced Enzymology, Biochemical Reasoning
- Thesis: "Anti-inflammatory Activities of Aqueous Extract of Avocado Pear Fruit in Male Wister Rats"

High School Diploma

Nigerian Tulip International College (NTIC), Ogun State

September 2009 - July 2015

Languages:

- Turkish (Beginner)
- English (Native)
- Yoruba (Native)

Certifications:

- Certificate of Biotechnology (SIIT), December 2020
- Certificate of Participation in a Business Workshop for WITO (NTIC), February 2021 Certificate of Jobberman Soft Skill Training, November 2022
- Certificate Code the Future (IBM), June 2023

Interests:

- Singing
- Reading novels

Additional Information:

- Volunteer Work: Participated in community health voluntary services during medical outreach programs in Lagos